The president of every bank.
they're in that room.
So go in there and convince them
that you're strong.
I'm the largest independent
oil producer in the region.
The only difference
between me and Monty
is I'm meaner.
Underestimating me is how
I buy you out.
I'm assuming you know
the sharks are circling.
Yeah. and they leave
a pretty big wake.
500 barrels a day.
$10 million dollars a year.
And it's ours.
This is the dream?
I did it for you.
Seems like you've been given
priority walk-on status
with the cheerleading corps.
I got in?
You are president
of an oil company.
It's time you start
living like it.
We're on a fucking Gulfstream.
I am living it.
Dorothy passed. T.L.
She's in a better place.
I'm sure you'll see her again.
If I do. that means
I'm in hell. too.
Who died?
My mother.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
- Should be getting close.
- Yup.
We're approaching
target formation!
Pressure's really running now.
Buddy. your well's kicking.
- You think it or you know it?
- Gauges don't lie. buddy.
Got to shut the well
and activate the BOP.
I got it!
She's gonna blow!
I'm no geologist.
but I'd say that's
a pretty good place to drill.
Yeah. she's got that look
about her. don't she?
This is Cooper Norris.
Please leave me a message.
I'll get back to you.
I have been calling you
for hours.
What happened?
Well blew.
Are you hurt?
I can't.
I need you to answer
when I call.
Last time someone didn't answer
is 'cause
they were already gone.
You have to give me that.
Sorry. My phone died.
Why are you crying?
Every well hit.
Every one.
That doesn't happen.
Every well don't hit.
The dream that
keeps coming true.
That makes you sad?
Scared. more like it.
Scared how?
What the hell do I do now?
Well. right now. you're gonna
take all that shit off
and throw it away.
Then you're gonna go
in the backyard
and wash off
with the garden hose
'cause you ain't getting
in my shower like that.
I'm gonna go get you some soap.
Um. get dish soap.
Bodywash won't cut it.
You think I haven't
done this before?
I'll meet you out back.
These are my only work boots.
You're a rich guy now.
You can afford new boots.
I don't think
we should do this anymore.
I thought I lost you. too.
For four hours.
with a panic burning
through me like acid.
I guess that means
I do love you.
But it looks like
I lost you after all.
I don't want to shop
for a new house.
I like this one.
My husband died for it.
I want my son to know his
abuelita. his cousins. I...
I have friends here. I don't
want to trade them for new ones.
I'm so glad
your dream came true.
I really am.
But being rich isn't my dream.
It's yours.
Hey. don't put no sausage in it.
Bior. what did I say?
Does this look like
a restaurant to you?
I don't eat no fucking swine.
Then don't eat it.
Who paid for the mix?
Who paid for the pan?
- It ain't swine. It's venison.
- What?
Deer meat.
Yeah. hell no.
I ain't eating that shit.
You eat steak?
- Yeah.
- Chicken?
I eat all that.
I just don't eat animals
that roll in they own shit.
And I damn sure don't eat
no animal you shot
and threw in the bed
of your motherfucking pickup.
What you making?
- Breakfast burritos.
- Mmm.
With deer meat.
These fools thinking
we living out on the prairie.
There's a McDonald's
five miles from here.
Oh. that shit's poison.
But venison
is about as organic as it gets.
No chemicals. no pesticides.
That's clean fuel right there.
Mmm.
All right. make this shit to-go.
- We got a long drive.
- You bet.
And you. you hurry your ass up
and get dressed.
We need to hit
a drive-through on the way.
You know what?
Give me Jorrell's.
That whiny motherfucker
ain't gonna eat his.
We'll meet you in the truck.
and don't fuck around.
- McDonald's.
- Yeah. all right.
I got you. Hurry your ass up.
Hey. Hold up. man.
Come on. move your ass.
Hey.
Tommy.
You working
the coyote field today?
- Yes. sir.
- That Barlow Brothers
outfit bankrupted.
- Mm-hmm.
- Their lease.
right beside ours.
could be bought
for 60 cents on the dollar.
so I want to get some eyes
out there on it.
see how much work it'd be
for us to take it over.
You know those pumpjacks
gonna be held together
with bailing wire.
Yeah. that's why it's
60 cents on the dollar. Boss.
Yeah.
Anyhow. I'm gonna have. uh.
Dale out there with you.
so look under every rock.
all right?
All right.
You heading out that way?
No. I'm driving up north.
Gonna plan a funeral.
Sorry to hear that.
Well. that's 'cause
you never met her.
I'll see you later.
- All right. Be safe.
- Yeah.
Um. I think you should
take all that money
and buy your own house.
I don't think you should
stay here anymore.
Drill. baby.
drill. baby. drill. baby. drill.
We are nine months
into a new administration.
and the boom is on.
Or is it? Oil prices
have dropped by over 20%
since our new administration
pushed initiatives
to increase production
domestically. as well as...
The cost of gasoline dropping
gives people more money
to spend on other goods.
And when diesel drops.
cost of the goods
goes down. too.
Well. the flip side
to that argument
is when fuel costs go down.
the cost of goods goes down.
So. it has a magnifying effect
to the strength of the dollar.
as well as how many dollars
you have to spend.
Thank you.
You still got to
get it out of the ground.
The cost of
getting it out of the ground
- goes down as well.
- There's a sweet spot. though.
and we are dancing on that line.
The line moves. too. dipshit.
Just play a fucking song.
for God's sake.
Well.
they don't pay us to talk. Bob.
They pay us
to play country music.
- That's right. Bob.
- Just trying
to have an intelligent
conversation. All right.
Well. Bob. you failed.
Let's kick off the hour
with some local boys
who made good. real good.
Oh. damn good. Took their
Texas sound nationwide.
I like them.
For God's sake.
play the fucking song!
Hey. honey. I'm gonna
have to call you back.
I'm arguing
with two of the dumbest
- sons of bitches in West Texas.
- Can they see me?
No. they can't see you.
They're on the radio.
You're arguing with someone
through the radio?
On the radio.
These fucking DJs haven't
played a song in 20 minutes.
They're yipping
like fucking lapdogs.
If you want to meet
the stupidest
son of a bitch in West Texas.
why don't you take a peek
in the rearview mirror.
and I'll introduce you to him?
Stop yelling at the radio
- and pay attention to me.
- Here we go.
- Hi. honey.
- Hi.
You okay?
Yeah. I'm fine.
You want to talk about it?
There's nothing to talk about.
- You sure?
- Yes. I'm sure.
People die.
It happens every day.
Yeah. but you left
without saying goodbye.
It's a long drive. sweetheart.
See. but I could've
kissed it better.
Then you would be relaxed
and not arguing with your radio.
Well. honey. I don't even think
that would've made this
a shorter drive.
Hey. little in life is certain.
but never in human history
has a man felt worse
after a blowjob.
especially mine.
Well. you got
a good point there.
You want a peek to cheer you up?
Honey. can I. can I just
please drive the fucking truck
and get where I'm going.
all right?
- Whoo!
- All right. now listen.
if we're gonna do this.
can you kind of elongate
the process a little bit.
so I can see something?
I'll see you tonight.
I love you.
You're an evil woman.
you know that?
Oh. shit.
H-H-Hey. bud.
I'm sorry. I-I meant to call.
Uh. hey. I need to see you.
Need some advice.
Girl advice or business advice?
Both.
Sounds like you and me
are having the same week.
Where are you?
Patch Café.
Well. can it wait till tonight?
I'm halfway to Lamesa.
They'll both still be
problems tonight.
They'll just be bigger.
All right. well. why don't you
get yourself some breakfast?
I'll-I'll be there
in an hour. all right?
All right.
Are you Cami Miller?
And who are you?
Hey. turn around!
- Whoa. whoa. whoa. hey. hey.
- Get on the fucking ground!
- I-I'm an agent of the court.
- Get on the ground!
- Car.
- Clear.
Hey. Cami Miller.
you've been served.
Hey. bear with us. Cami.
We're reading this over.
At best.
it's a simple breach case.
don't you think?
Purple. white.
Horned Frogs. fight.
Is there any way
to turn that off?
To date. no one has successfully
found the switch.
Mrs. Miller. it appears
there was a gas well
off the coast of Louisiana
that blew out.
M-TEX received
a $420 million dollar settlement
from the insurance company.
but the policy stipulates
the money be spent
- on drilling another well.
- Cami.
there are timelines
that must be met.
Geological survey
by a certain point.
environmental review
by another point.
Typically.
the insurance company pays
as new expenses are incurred.
but in this instance.
they paid the entire settlement
in advance.
Well. where's that money now?
Well. that's what
we need to find out.
Let us do some digging.
I'll reach out
to plaintiff's attorney
and explain our change
of control and intent to comply.
Intent to comply?
What do you mean?
Comply to what?
It means
we need to drill a gas well
out in the ocean. Cami.
and we got to do it
pretty quick.
So. let us circle up over here.
and I'll come to Fort Worth
tomorrow and walk you
through all this.
Nate. you and Rebecca stay
on the line.
all right?
Call me back. Tommy.
Yes. ma'am. I will.
You thinking what I'm thinking?
Now we know where the money came
from for the workover fields.
Rebecca. you go to Fort Worth.
sit with plaintiff's attorney
'cause if this stuff gets out.
banks will start calling notes.
I should be
in that meeting. Tommy.
Rebecca doesn't have any
experience in offshore drilling
or the timelines required
to get a project like this
up and running.
Nate. we don't have
the $400 million to drill.
She don't need experience
with offshore drilling.
She needs experience
with bullshitting.
So. Rebecca. you get us as much
lead time as possible.
And. Nate. you find
the money. all right?
I'll talk to y'all later.
Chuck Parker is an
offshore drilling engineer.
Give him a call.
Take the four hours
to Fort Worth
to become as big an expert
as you can.
And so you understand?
- Mm-hmm.
- Drilling an offshore well
within a year is warp speed.
Mm-hmm. Got it.
No. you don't got it.
They're gonna want a timeline.
and you have no concept
of what that is.
Ever heard
of the word "feasibility"?
How about "diligence"?
Or "earnest"?
Or the phrase "best efforts"?
I can negotiate
a drilling agreement
on the fucking moon
and make the entire contract
contingent upon us
fucking getting there.
You are on the wrong side of
this company's chain of command
to raise your voice at me.
Don't ever do it again.
Hi.
Oh. man. A few weeks off from
a sport. boy. do you feel it.
Cheerleading is a sport now?
It's always been a sport.
Isn't the purpose
to cheer on other sports?
We cheer for all the sports...
football. basketball.
soccer even.
We don't cheer for gymnastics.
but most of us
used to be gymnasts.
We just grew.
so maybe that's why.
We don't cheer for track.
and we don't cheer for baseball
for some reason.
I think there's just
nowhere for us to stand.
so I guess. actually. we just
cheer for football. basketball.
and sometimes soccer.
And ourselves.
When we're at
cheerleading competitions.
we cheer for the cheerleaders
who are cheering.
It's best just to...
That's nice. Very...
- It's a very selfless sport.
- Mm-hmm.
I think so.
It's kind of like
an emotional support group.
but with acrobatics.
- Morning. Neil.
- Nate.
You know what I'm gonna do?
I'm gonna get you a name tag.
Or you could memorize it.
See. I think in a past life.
I knew a Neil
who looked just like you.
That must be it.
Mama. I need to change
real quick.
We have aerobics
with the old folk. honey.
They'll love that.
- You think so?
- If I had legs
like yours. I'd wear that
son of a bitch to church.
You do have legs like mine.
just longer.
Bye. Rebecca.
When you raise them right. Neil.
the joy they give you
is endless.
Nate.
Gonna get you a name tag.
We need an office.
On that. you and I
are in complete agreement.
Do you have any interest. ma'am?
Oh. I-I read the news
on my computer.
C-Can you have Kevin
bring the car around?
Where should I tell him
you're going?
My husband's office.
You look tired.
You going up through
Lubbock or Snyder?
Don't make much difference.
Go up through Snyder.
I need to show you something.
What do you know. bud?
I know that your son
is the luckiest son of a bitch
- I ever met.
- Is that a fact?
And I met a few.
Lucky how?
This is mine.
Yours?
Cobbled together some leases.
put together a crew.
We've drilled six so far.
Six?
And this one hit?
They all hit.
Marty. you worked these over?
We drilled new ones.
These was all shallow.
Tommy. we started hitting
just shy of 6.000 feet.
This one's 6.700.
and she'll push
3.500 barrels a day.
All in. how much?
About 7.000 barrels a day.
See my problem?
Can I have a minute. Marty?
- Yeah. Good to see you. bud.
- Good to see you. Marty.
So. what do I do now?
You're eight million a well
to drill here.
Who paid for this?
There's a company in Odessa
that financed
the spec wells 50-50 to recoup
and 18% after that.
On what fucking planet
does a company
finance drilling at 50-50
and reduces to 18?
What did you put up?
I don't have anything to put up.
They financed the whole thing?
Yeah.
What is this company?
- Sonrisa.
- Never heard of it.
And I sure as fuck
ain't heard of Esteban Galvez.
You got a contract?
In the truck.
Did you get a lawyer
to go over it?
Well...
Son. why didn't you come to me?
I'm coming to you now.
- Well. it's too fucking late.
- Well. what were you gonna do?
If I came to you. at best.
you would have had me tied up
in geological surveys
for the next year.
You're goddamn right I do.
Good Lord Almighty.
You spend $40 million dollars
drilling holes in the ground.
not having a fucking clue
what's underneath.
A new restaurant
has a better success rate
than blind drilling.
Well. I want to have
a look at this contract
to see how they fucked you.
I'll take you to their office.
Oh. I'm going to their office.
You can bet your ass on that.
but not today.
I got to pick out a casket.
I should pick out one for you.
Here. you drive. I'll read.
Hey. Cooper.
Why here?
All these old wells
were shallow.
1.500 to 4.000 feet.
They were all still producing.
Not much. but something.
If the field was drying up.
they wouldn't be all producing.
It means
pressure's pushing it up.
It just made sense to go deeper.
Made sense to you.
That's what I said.
- Hey.
I'm still waiting to hear back
from the accountants.
but all the contracts here
and related wires
are the business accounts
at Chase.
I can't find any payment from
Blanton hitting that account.
And I don't have any transfers
from the holding accounts
for those funds.
Hey. listen. have you ever heard
of a financial services company
out of Odessa called Sonrisa?
Sonrisa?
Yeah. it's a-a petroleum lender.
I'll send you a picture
- of the business card.
- Okay.
I want you to find out
everything you can about them.
I mean. when it was founded.
who founded it.
who's underwriting it.
the whole deal.
This have to do
with the default on Blanton?
No. No. this is something else.
Anyway. I'll talk to you later.
but just get on that. will you?
- Okay.
- All right. Bye.
Okay. so. I understand
your business problem.
Let's talk about
your girl problem.
Well. I told her the wells hit.
we can move off.
start a new life
with no worries.
Let me guess.
she don't want a new life.
She kicked me out of the house.
Let me tell you something
about women.
When they do
something irrational.
like kick you out of the house.
you got to sit them down
and give them
a goddamn good listening to.
The girl's life's
been shattered.
And however she wants
to put it back together.
that's her business.
You don't have a say.
So you just listen and let her
put it back together
however she sees fit. all right?
I think the money scares her.
Shit. you don't have
any money yet.
And I got a feeling
that you've already been fucked
out of what you should get.
And she ain't wrong about
being scared of the money.
It ruins more families
than it fixes. Trust me.
Your girl problem
is a lot easier
than your business problem.
All you got to do
is ask and listen.
and remember what she said...
and then make it come true.
Now stretch high in the sky.
grab at a star.
Now other arm. reach high.
Bob.
Sorry.
Oof.
I don't need you
shitting on that sofa. Bob.
- I just had it cleaned.
- I'm wearing my diaper.
Okay.
Now arms out to the side.
Make little circles.
Now the other way.
- That's so silly.
- Then we're gonna
- flap our wings.
- Ooh!
Now flap your wings.
Feel it. Yes.
- Butterflies.
- We're not gliding. Bob.
We're flying.
Work those wings. baby.
Almost there.
Okay. Yes!
And done.
Good job.
Okay. now. everybody up.
Oh. geez.
The bar is open!
- The bar's open.
- The bar is open.
The bar is open.
- What is it?
- Gin and coconut juice.
Oh. wow!
They drink this in the Bahamas.
A gin a day keeps
the malaria away.
We ain't got no malaria here.
This is West Texas.
You can never be too sure. Bob.
All right.
time to shake that ass. Beverly.
- Oh. okay. Okay.
- Let's see it.
- Here goes. And it goes...
- Let's go. Bev.
Yes!
Ah! Oh. money!
Come on. ladies! Work it. yes.
Don't be getting handsy. Hank.
- I'm trying not to.
- Put them in your pocket. Hank.
- Aww.
- In the pocket. There you go.
I think the strip club
awoke the demon in Hank.
Well. there's nothing wrong
with a little demon.
is there. Hank?
- Oh. no.
- Mm-mm. No pocket pool.
You're getting real close
to a time-out.
Ooh!
I'm Inspector Hayes
with the THHSC.
Our inspection
is scheduled for next week.
- We're early.
- What's with the music?
Aerobics.
Oh. I don't think
we should inter... Oh. God.
Yes!
- Yes!
- What in the...
What?
It's...
an interpretive dance class.
Who provided the alcohol?
I ain't saying shit.
You know. it's...
It's not like they aren't
old enough to drink.
Ma'am. we will get to you
in a minute.
Sit down over there.
You can't tell her what to do.
We don't work here.
We're just guests.
Ma'am. we have authority over
the safety of this facility.
You're what.
the fucking old people police?
Hey. You. go sit down.
- Make me.
- Mom.
- Honey.
- Ma'am?
- Mom?
- Honey?
When I say sit down. I mean...
Oh!
Oh. my God.
- Oh. my God.
- Oh. shit.
- Old people police
just got they asses kicked.
Have a seat. Miss Falcone.
Did I say it correctly?
You did.
We appreciate you
taking this so seriously.
but the time to carve out a deal
has passed you by.
This is going to trial.
Well. this will go
before an arbitration committee.
according to the contract.
But before that.
we will terminate
all of our policies
with your client
and cease the $14 million
in annual premiums we pay.
then we will file
for bankruptcy protection.
where you will stand
at the back of the line
because you have
no real damages.
We suffered a loss.
and you paid a claim.
as you were legally bound to do.
The fact that we have to drill
as stipulated is irrelevant.
Or we sell the company
to a Diamondback.
or XTO or... God help you...
BP or Chevron.
and they shove
this bullshit claim
so far up your ass you can
taste the ink on the summons.
I assume you know
the principal is deceased.
The new principal
had no knowledge
of this requirement
of the policy.
nor did she know of
an insurance claim on the rig.
nor did she know of the rig.
You are suing the grieving widow
of the company owner.
Please seek to move this
out of arbitration.
I can't wait
to put her on the stand.
She can cry on cue.
It's uncanny.
You with Shepherd-Hastings.
I was. I'm in-house
for the company now.
- Will you outsource litigation?
- Not on your life.
Look. Rebecca. uh.
if I may call you that...
- You just did.
- Okay. tiger.
Look. we all knew Monty.
and we're not exactly sure
how he got them to pay out
the entire claim at once
and directly to him.
but it has set a precedent
my client is very serious
about reversing.
We need to make
a bit of an example here.
Well. if a claim was
improperly paid by your client.
that is a violation
of the contract.
which nullifies
any subsequent damages clause.
It doesn't matter that my client
didn't apply the funds
as stipulated.
The contract states
that the funds
be sent directly
to the drilling company
as expenses are incurred.
Your client violated
that agreement.
Your damages are not real.
and even if they were.
your client's
intentional violation
of the contract
suspends the damages clause.
How do we know your client
didn't misrepresent the funds...
Well. he certainly
misrepresented something.
didn't he. and your client bit.
to the tune of
$400 million dollars.
so if you want to take whacks
at a dead man
in front of a jury
and his widow?
I'm in.
I'm ready.
I like that kind of party.
I don't hear a proposal.
You will.
as soon as you concede.
one. you have no damages.
And two. your client's
violation of the contract
supersedes our violation
and negates any damages
you would have been entitled to
if there were damages
to begin with.
- I still don't hear a proposal.
- We will issue a press release
announcing the drill and endure
all the scrutiny that entails
to publicly satisfy
your client's bruised ego.
Timeline.
I need a geological survey
and a feasibility report
before I can even begin to...
Don't feed us that bullshit.
Now you're playing
in our sandbox.
You know exactly
where you're drilling
because you already
had a rig there.
and if it wasn't
for a hurricane.
you'd still have a rig there.
You need to lease a rig.
two tugboats and hire a crew.
We want weekly progress reports.
and in those reports.
I want progress.
Under those terms...
we will submit
a request to dismiss.
Agreed.
Rebecca.
You're on the wrong side
of this game.
Counsel for an independent
producer is just Whac-A-Mole.
They're wildcatters. gamblers.
They'd lie to their mothers
to secure a lease.
The wise ones sell out.
go sleep on a mattress of money.
Monty wasn't wise.
Lot of skeletons in that closet.
Look. when the floor
falls out from beneath you...
and it will...
you give us a call.
We thought our case
was pretty cut-and-dry
until you carved it to pieces.
I'm happy where I am.
I highly doubt that.
Be sure to grab my card
on your way out.
$2.400 for a box.
Well. what do you think?
I don't know coffins.
Well. shit.
I ain't no expert myself.
When I buy this one.
it'll be my first.
You can just cremate me. spread
me over the Palo Duro Canyon.
Sounds pretty good.
I might steal that one.
Fuck.
Walt. what are you doing
FaceTiming me?
I want to show you something.
Hi. baby.
Hi. Daddy.
- What the fuck?
- Don't be mad.
- Right?
- Angela...
I mean. suddenly. it's a crime
to defend yourself.
Defend yourself against what?
Hold on.
All right.
I'll be right back. Cooper.
Hey. Walt?
Just walk me through it.
Apparently. these Health
and Human Service inspectors
walked in on a bunch
of 80-year-olds
who were drinking
and dirty dancing.
- They tried to get your wife...
- Hey. hey.
just let me talk to Angie.
Hey. what happened?
That son of a bitch
tried to grab me
and shove me on the couch.
So you...
I-I kneed him in his nuts
and elbowed him
in his fat fucking head.
What about the other one?
Well. she just tripped.
I mean.
she didn't see my foot. I guess.
Baby. you say it
just like that in court.
Good girl. Hey. Walt?
Do these nursing home
inspectors have badges?
I don't know about badges.
They have the power
to arrest and detain?
They do not.
All right. so it was just some
fat fuck grabbing my wife. then.
Here's what I want you to do.
I want you to uncuff them
right now
and let them go.
unless you want my new counsel
to be your newest hemorrhoid.
So do...
What are you standing there for?
Just fucking uncuff them. bud.
Don't yell at me.
I just got here.
You think that's yelling?
That's not yelling.
This is yelling: uncuff
my fucking wife
and my fucking daughter
and let them go right now.
do you understand me?
Told you. Walt.
All right. Cory?
Supper's gonna be
a little late tonight. baby.
I'm sorry.
That's okay. baby.
All right. I'll see you later.
I love you. Daddy.
Yeah. I love you. too. Bye.
You won't believe this shit.
I thought I heard yelling.
Oh. that was just me
purging my grief.
We'll take that one right there.
It's a nice choice.
Uh. yeah. Yeah.
Would you like to choose
some flower arrangements?
I'm funeraled out.
to tell you the truth.
Why don't you just pick
the flowers? All right?
We need to go see
your grandfather. son.
Uh. how many would you like?
Oh. uh. I don't know.
uh. enough to say I tried.
not enough to say I miss her.
Okay. Uh...
You know what makes
the sunsets in West Texas
so goddamn spectacular?
They're not like this
everywhere?
Mm-mm.
It's a combination of dust
and the lack of moisture
in the air.
Shorter wavelengths of light
are filtered away.
leaving the red and orange.
Lack of water and dust.
Two things that make living here
so fucking unbearable.
Place hates us all day
and then gives us this.
Can't make any sense of it.
Not sure we're supposed to.
You're not supposed to.
I'm 82 years old.
and sitting in this chair
hurts like a fucking car crash.
Wondering is all I got left.
What about you?
You do an honest day's work.
or are you cheating the world
like your old man?
I guess I'm a cheater like him.
Yeah. It figures.
Look how far the apple falls.
Picked out a casket. You want
to look at a picture of it?
I'll bet you can't wait to get
it in the ground. can you?
We've avoided telling each other
the truth for a long time.
Let's not start now.
You'll ruin it.
I can't understand why
everybody wants to ruin it.
It's a disease. you know?
For some people.
For her.
And it killed
a part of her I loved
and left us
with the woman you knew.
But I remember
when she was the brightest light
everywhere she went.
Ain't never seen
a sunset prettier.
Well.
the sun had already set
by the time I was born.
Funeral's Friday.
I never got to meet her.
but I wish I could have.
It's best you didn't.
I'll see you Friday. I guess.
See you then.
You know. it was probably best
that I only had you ever
on the weekend.
I wasn't raised to father a son.
And all your grandfather did
was work himself
into being a cripple
out on the rigs.
Come home and get drunk enough
to deal with my damn
coked-out tornado of a mother.
And then come in my room and...
try to beat his failures
all out of me.
If you gonna raise
that girl's boy.
or one of your own.
just know this:
uh. however you raise your son
is how he's gonna raise his son.
And that cycle is...
almost impossible to break.
You broke it.
I avoided it.
I love you. Dad.
You did your best. and...
your best is good enough for me.
You got a light?
Yeah. Yeah. it's right there.
Thanks.
It was a hot one today.
wasn't it?
- It was warm.
- Yeah.
All right. What a day.
Oh. I'm sorry. boys.
I got arrested.
and let me tell you.
that will wreck an afternoon.
Ainsley?
Honey. I need your help.
- Wait. did you say...
- Long story. Dale.
It was self-defense.
- What was self-defense?
- Well.
a man grabbed Mama.
and that only works out one way.
I have no doubt.
Do I need to call anyone?
No. Daddy has it handled.
Everything that ends well
is well.
Uh...
I think I have that backwards.
You do. Uh. but we get
the spirit of the statement.
Baby. I need you.
Just remember. the hungrier
you are. the better it'll taste.
Mm-hmm. Oh. shit.
Supper's gonna be a chain gang
theme. I guess. tonight.
The only logical explanation
for this situation
is a test from God.
- That's all I can come up with.
- What do y'all think
about sloppy joes?
- Great.
Great.
Oil futures
are down three percent today
to 725 as OPEC
increases production
in an attempt to drive
prices down and slow
the expansion of oil production
in the Permian Basin.
But the American
Petroleum Institute
touts more efficient and
automated drilling techniques
allow profits
at lower prices per barrel.
though admits
that a trade war with OPEC
harms producers
both here and abroad.
Ram. bah. zoo.
Lickety. lickety. zoo. zoo.
Who. wah. wah. who.
Give 'em hell. TCU!
Let's go. Frogs!
Let's go. TCU!
Let's give 'em hell!
Let's go. Frogs!
Let's go. Purple!
- This is my hell.
- Riff. ram. bah. zoo.
Lickety. lickety. zoo. zoo.
Who. wah. wah. who.
Give 'em hell. TCU.
Let's go. TCU!
Riff. ram. bah. zoo.
Lickety. lickety. zoo. zoo.
Who. wah. wah. who.
Give 'em hell. TCU!
Let's go. Purple!
What the frick
are you doing here?
You know. you're 18 now.
You can say "fuck."
I can. but I choose not to.
Keeping my mouth clean.
I doubt that.
You know. it comforts me
that you'll die of lung cancer.
I just wish it would
happen soon.
- Like today.
- Well. who knows?
Maybe I'll step out
in front of a bus.
Would you. please? Let me guess.
The widow finally
came to her senses.
- You don't mention her name.
- I don't know her name.
Why'd she kick you out?
She finally see you
in the daylight?
No. actually.
she found out we were related.
- Keep smoking. Cooper.
- Mm.
You let Cooper
sleep on the couch?
Now we have to get it cleaned.
Well. honey. he's had
a rough couple of days. Be nice.
What about my couple of days?
- Huh?
- Sweetheart. you got accepted
to college and went
day-drinking with your mother.
- What's wrong with those days?
- And then
attacked and incarcerated.
You were detained.
You weren't incarcerated. okay?
Sure. Daddy. Sure.
Take the world's side!
Excuse me.
I had a dream last night...
that you moved to Fort Worth.
Actually. all of you.
Your wife. your daughter.
It's a dream
you should consider coming true.
You have that power.
This is what I found on Sonrisa.
Money comes from a fund
in Dallas. is my best guess.
This is the fund manager.
He formed the LLC.
Let me know
if you need anything else.
Okay. I will. Thanks. bud.
Morning.
You know who this is?
No.
That's your new partner.
And it's a real
fucking problem. son.
Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-